VALERIE CATUBAY

FULL STACK DEVELOPER/OUTSYSTEMS DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+639688949999 valerie.catubay@phoenix-dx.com https://github.com/valeriesalvador

SKILLS

C#

Outsystems

Node/Typescript

Angular/React

Javascript

HTML/CSS

DBMS/SQL/Mysql/PostgreSQL/MongoDB REST API Development and Integration

Stripe/Paypal

Wordpress

Zoho

Python

PHP5

Firebase

AWS(S3, EC2, Elastic Beanstalk)

GIT

JIRA/Azure/Hubspot/Clickup/Trello

EDUCATION

BATAAN PENINSULA STATE UNIVERSITY **2013-2017**

BS Information Technology

PROFILE

I have over 8 years of experience in software development, focusing on both backend and frontend technologies. My goal is to deliver user-friendly products and help companies turn their visions into reality. I've worked across various industries, including Medical, Ecommerce, Government, Insurance, Multimedia, and Marketing, allowing me to provide valuable technical insights on related projects.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Outsystems Developer

2023 - Current | PhoenixDX

<u>Area of Expertise: Responsible for Outsystems Reactive</u> <u>Development</u>

As a Senior OutSystems Developer, I have been responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining robust and scalable applications using the OutSystems low-code platform. My role involves collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality solutions, enhancing system performance, and ensuring a seamless user experience.

Senior Software Developer/Outsystems Developer 2021 – 2023 | Weava

Area of Expertise: Responsible for Stripe Integration and Maintenance in the application

Working with a group of experienced professionals in developing a chrome extension using Outsystems, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Angular and React. Weava has more than 700,000 users at the moment.

Mid Software Developer

2020-2021 | AFS Dynamics

Area of Expertise: Responsible for building the architecture & design of every project.

Working as a sole developer of this startup company based in Canada. We cater to different clients in Canada for their software development needs including Etsy and DesignBeetle.

Software Developer

2018-2020 | Direct Sourcing Solutions

<u>Area of Expertise: Responsible for tasks that involves</u>

<u>creating metrices dashboards.</u>

Collaboration with an agile team consisting of 6 professionals to deliver projects for our clients mostly based in Hongkong. Most of the notable projects we did are store marketing dashboards for Chanel. PruLife HK and Asurion.